Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Event documentation, 1968-2015
  - Events, 1977
    - Winter Folk Festival, December 1977
      - Moving Images, 1977-12-09 to 1977-12-10
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77 1210_3; Note on media: Balkan Arts Center concert #3
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77 1210_4; Note on media: Balkan Arts Center party - dance
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77 1210_5; Note on media: Balkan Arts Center Romanian dancing
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77 1210_6; Note on media: Balkan Arts Center - Song [?] workshop; Greek workshop with band #1
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77 1210_7; Note on media: Balkan Arts Center - Greek workshop with band #2
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77 1210_8; Note on media: Balkan Festival - Greek workshop #2; Romanian workshop
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77-1210_1-2-3; Note on media: 1: Halkias 2: Sven Lusani (Northern Albanian) 3: Bob Warner (Scandinavian fiddle) 4: Banat Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77-1210_4-5-6; Note on media: 1: Halkias 2: Banat and dance workshop 3: singing workshop with Ethel Raim 4: Greek dance workshop with Halkias
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 94 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 77-1210_7-8; Note on media: 1: Greek dance workshop with Halkias (continued) 2: dancing with Banat
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., WFF 77-1210_7-8
      - Sound Recordings, 1977-12-10
        - 1 sound reel (original): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 77-1210-1
        - 1 sound reel (original): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 77-1210-3
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 77-1210-1a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 77-1210-1b, 2a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 77-1210-2b, 3 RD
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 77-1210-1,2a-TD (Box 18)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 77-1210-2b,3-TD (Box 18)
        - 12 audio files (wav): digital., WFF77-1210-2b_3
    - Other events, 1977
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1977-08-27; 1977-09-30, BAC 77-0827/0930; Note on folder: Balkan Festival & Folk Dance Party (Box-folder 3/2)
        - 1 folder, 1977-09-30, FDF 77-0930; Note on folder: Gala Opening (Box-folder 3/3)
        - 1 folder, 1977-10-28, BAC 77-1028; Note on folder: Dance Song Workshop (Box-folder 3/5)
        - 1 folder, 1977-10-28, FDF 77-1028; Note on folder: Pontic-Greek Evening (Box-folder 3/4)
        - 1 folder, 1977-11-25, FDF 77-1125; Note on folder: Galician Spanish Evening (Box-folder 3/6)
        - 1 folder, 1977-12-30, FDF 77-1230; Note on folder: Epirot Greek Evening (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Sound Recordings, 1977-12-01
        - 27 audio files (wav): digital., WFF77-1201-1_2a
  - Events, 1978
    - Macedonian Concert and Dance Party, March 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-03-05
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Moving Images, 1978-03-05
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0305_1; Note on media: Balkan Arts performance
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0305_2; Note on media: Balkan Arts performance
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0305_3; Note on media: Balkan Arts performance
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0305_4; Note on media: Balkan Arts performance
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0305_5; Note on media: Balkan Arts performance
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0305_1_2_3; Note on media: EMCS: Balkan Arts Performance
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 94 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0305_4_5; Note on media: EMCS: Balkan Arts Performance
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-0305_1-3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-0305_4_5; Note on media: Pitu Guli, et al.
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-03-06
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_1; Note on media: Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_1a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_1b, 2a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_2; Note on media: Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_2b RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_3; Note on media: Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_3a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_3b, 4a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_4b RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0306_5 RD
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0306-1,2a-TD (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0306-2b, 3a-TD (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0306-3b, 4-TD (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0306-5-TD (Box 15)
        - 15 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0306-1_2a-TD
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0306-2b_3a-TD
        - 5 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0306-3b_4-TD
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0306-5-TD
    - Yiddish Concert, March 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-03-12
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Moving Images, 1978-03-12
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_1; Note on media: Yiddish concert
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_2
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_3
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_4
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_1_2; Note on media: Feigl Yudin, Andy Statman, and Zev Feldman
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_3_4; Note on media: Feigl Yudin, Andy Statman and Zev Feldman
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-0312_1_2; Note on media: Feigl Yudin, Andy Statman and Zev Feldman
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-0312_3_4; Note on media: Feigl Yudin, Andy Statman and Zev Feldman
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-03-12
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_1; Note on media: Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_1a
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_2; Note on media: Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-0312_2a
        - 1 sound disc (CD), EMCS 78-0312-1-TD; Note on media: Feigl Yudin, Andy Statman and Zev Feldman (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), EMCS 78-0312-2-TD; Note on media: Feigl Yudin, Andy Statman and Zev Feldman (Box 15)
        - 16 audio files (wav): digital., EMCS78-0312-1-TD
        - 13 audio files (wav): digital., EMCS78-0312-2-TD
    - Banat Workshop / Jorgovan Orchestra, March 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-03-31
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-03-31
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0331_1a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0331_2; Note on media: Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0331_2a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0331_2b, 1b RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0331_3; Note on media: Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0331_3 RD
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0331-1-TD (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0331-2-TD (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0331-3-TD (Box 15)
        - 15 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0331-1-TD
        - 18 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0331-2-TD
        - 5 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0331-3-TD
    - Irish Dance Workshop, April 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-04-28
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-04-28
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0428_01; Note on media: Ceili Dance
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0428; Note on media: Folk Dance Fridays: Irish Night (Box 15)
        - 22 audio files (wav): digital., BAC-78-0428-CD1
    - Zenska Pensa: Balkan Women's Song, May 1978
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-05-07
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0507_1; Note on media: Workshop - Zenska Penza, Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0507_1 RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0507_2a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0507_2b RD
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC -78-0507-1-TD (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC -78-0507-2-TD (Box 15)
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0507-1-TD
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-0507-2-TD
    - Folk Dance Fridays: Balkan Concert and Dance, May 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-05-19
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Epirot Greek Evening (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Moving Images, 1978-05-19
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: FDF 78-0519_1; Note on media: Zenska Pesna (Woman’s Song)
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: FDF 78-0519_1-3; Note on media: Halkias Family Orchestra
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: FDF 78-0519_2
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: FDF 78-0519_3; Note on media: Zenska Pesna (Woman’s Song)
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FDF 78-0519-1-2-3
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-05-19
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-0519-1,2-TD; Note on media: Halkias Family Orchestra (Box 15)
    - Queens Ethnic Music Festival, June 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-06-10
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Photographs
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Moving Images, 1978-06-10
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_1; Note on media: Balkans
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_2
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_3
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_4
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_6
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_7
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_8
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_1-2-3-4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 78-0610_1-4
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-06-10
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_1
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_2
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_3
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_4
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_5
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_6
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_7
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_8
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_9
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_10
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_11
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_12
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_1a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_1b, 2a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_2b RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_3a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_3b, 4a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_4b RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_4c, 5a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_5b, 6a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_6b RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_7a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_7b, 8a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_8b RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_9a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_9b, 10a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_10b RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_10c, 11a RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_11b RD
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: QFF 78-0610_12 RD
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-1,2a-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-2b-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-3,4a-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-4b,5-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-6, 7a-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-7b,8-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-9,10a-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-10b,11,12a-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), QFF 78-0610-12-TD (Box 17)
        - 8 audio files (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-1_2a-TD
        - 6 audio files (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-2b-TD
        - 16 audio files (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-3_4a-TD
        - 21 audio file (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-4b_5-TD
        - 20 audio files (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-6_7a-TD
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-7b_8-TD
        - 9 audio files (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-9_10a-TD
        - 26 audio files (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-10b_11-TD
        - 16 audio files (wav): digital., QFF78-0610-12-TD
    - Folk Dance Fridays: Pontic Greek Dance with Papadopoulos Orchestra, October 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-10-27
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-10-27
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-1027_1b, 2a
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-1027_2b
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-1027_3; Note on media: Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-1027_3 RD
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-1027-1,2a-TD (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 78-1027-3,2b-TD (Box 15)
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-1027-1_2a-TD
        - 10 audio files (wav): digital., BAC78-1027-3_2b-TD
    - Jewish Klezmer Music: Tribute to Dave Tarras, November 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-11-19
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Moving Images, 1978-11-19
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_1
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_2
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_3
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_4
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_3; Note on media: includes tribute and dance party
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_1_2_3
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_4
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-1119_1_2_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-1119_v1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-1119_v2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-1119_v3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS 78-1119_4
        - 1 video disc (DVD), EMCS 78-1119-1-3 DVD (Box 19)
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS_78-1119-1-3-DVD_title01
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS_78-1119-1-3-DVD_title02
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS_78-1119-1-3-DVD_title03
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS_78-1119-1-3-DVD_title04
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., EMCS_78-1119-1-3-DVD_title05
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-11-19
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_1; Note on media: Jewish klezmer (1 of 3), Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_2; Note on media: Jewish klezmer (2 of 3), Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_3; Note on media: Jewish klezmer (3 of 3), Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 7 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119_4; Note on media: Klezmer music lecture; presentation, Casa Galicia
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119-1a
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119-1b, 2a
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1119-2b, 3a
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: EMCS 78-1118_3b
        - 1 sound disc (CD), EMCS 78-1119-1; Note on media: Klezmer Lecture/Demonstration with Zev Feldman (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), EMCS 78-1119-2; Note on media: Klezmer Lecture/Demonstration with Zev Feldman (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), EMCS 78-1119-1a,1b,2a (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), EMCS 78-1119-2b, 3a, 3b (Box 15)
        - 12 audio files (wav): digital., EMCS 78-1119-1
        - 6 audio files (wav): digital., EMCS 78-1119-2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., EMCS78-1119-1a_1b_2a
        - 3 audio files (wav): digital., EMCS78-1119-2b_3a_3b
    - Winter Folk Festival, December 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1978-12-01
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Eleventh Annual Winter Folk Festival (Box-folder 3/26)
      - Photographs, 1978-12-01
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Sound Recordings, 1978-12-02 to 1978-12-03
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1202_1; Note on media: Folk Music in America
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1202_1a; Note on media: Folk Music in America
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1202_1b; Note on media: Folk Music in America
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1202_2; Note on media: Bulgarian Music and Song (presentation)
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1202_2a; Note on media: Bulgarian Music and Song (presentation)
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1202_2b; Note on media: Bulgarian Music and Song (presentation)
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1202_2c; Note on media: Bulgarian Music and Song (presentation)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 78-1202-1a-TD (Box 18)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 78-1202-1b,2a-TD; Note on media: Music, Dance, and Song in the Bulgarian Ritual Year (Box 18)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 78-1202-2b-TD (Box 18)
        - 12 audio files (wav): digital., WFF78-1202-1a-TD
        - 29 audio files (wav): digital., WFF78-1202-1b_2a-TD
        - 10 audio files (wav): digital., WFF78-1202-2b-TD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_1; Note on media: concert, 1 of 3 - Casa Galicia, New York City
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_1a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_1b, 2a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_2; Note on media: concert, 2 of 3 - Casa Galicia, New York City
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_2b RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_3; Note on media: concert, 3 of 3 - Casa Galicia, New York City
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_3a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_3b, 4a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_4; Note on media: dance party, 1 of 3 - Casa Galicia, New York City
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_4b RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_5; Note on media: dance party, 2 of 3 - Casa Galicia, New York City
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_5a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_5b, 6a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_6; Note on media: dance party, 3 of 3 - Casa Galicia, New York City
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_6b RD
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_7
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_7, 8a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_8
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 78-1203_8b RD
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 78-1203-1,2a-TD (Box 18)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 78-1203-2b,3a-TD (Box 18)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 78-1203-3b,4-TD (Box 18)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 78-1203-5,6-TD (Box 18)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 78-1203-7,8-TD; Note on media: Overlap Rolls (Box 18)
        - 19 audio files (wav): digital., WFF78-1203-1_2a-TD
        - 20 audio files (wav): digital., WFF78-1203-2b_3a-TD
        - 16 audio files (wav): digital., WFF78-1203-3b_4-TD
        - 18 audio files (wav): digital., WFF78-1203-5_6-TD
        - 16 audio files (wav): digital., WFF78-1203-7_8-TD
    - Other events, 1978
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 oversize folder, 1978, Note on media: Novo Selo (Container oversize folder 1)
        - 1 folder, 1978, Note on folder: Popovich Brothers of South Chicago (Box-folder 3/10)
        - 1 folder, 1978-01-27, FDF 78-0127; Note on folder: Caucasus Dance Workshop (Box-folder 3/11)
        - 1 folder, 1978-02-24, FDF 78-0224; Note on folder: Pontic Greek Dance Workshop (Box-folder 3/12)
        - 1 folder, 1978-03-19, EMCS 78-0319; Note on folder: Zenska Penska (Box-folder 3/15)
        - 1 folder, 1978-06-30, FDF 78-0630; Note on folder: Macedonian Folk Orchestra (Box-folder 3/20)
        - 1 folder, 1978-07, FDF 78-07; Note on folder: Folk Dance Fridays Summer (Box-folder 3/21)
        - 1 folder, 1978-09-29, FDF 78-0929; Note on folder: Macedonian Folk Orchestra (Box-folder 3/22)
        - 1 folder, 1978-11-24, FDF 78-1124; Note on folder: New England Contra Dance (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Photographs
        - 1 folder, 1978-03, FR 78-03; Note on folder: Martin Koenig in Montreal (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Moving Images
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., 1978-04-25, AFC 2014/044: BAC 78-0425
  - Events, 1979
    - Italian Concert and Dance Party, March 1979
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1979-03-25
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Photographs, 1979-03-25
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Moving Images, 1979-03-25
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 79-0325_1
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 79-0325_2